usedpriceinfo.com 2016-12-14

# Privacy Policy - Used Price Info

What This Privacy Policy Covers This policy covers how Used Price Info Co., Inc. (“Used Price Info”) treats personal information.

Information Collection and Use General There are several links from the Used Price Info Web site to third party information and service providers who may collect personal information from you in order to provide you with information or services. Used Price Info has no control over the privacy policy of any third party company, so please examine their privacy policy prior to submitting any personal information. This privacy policy applies to the Used Price Info Web site. 

When you visit Used Price Info pages, we may collect certain information about your visit from your browser, including the Internet Protocol (IP) address through which you access the Internet, the date and time you access the Used Price Info Web site, and the pages that you access while at the Used Price Info Web site.  
Used Price Info aggregates non-specific visitor information for statistical purposes, such as the production of the Used Price Info’s popular products list.  
This information is used to help improve the Used Price Info Web site, analyze trends, and administer the site.  

Used Price Info uses your non-personal information for the following general purposes: to customize the content and advertising you see, and to improve our services.  
Used Price Info also uses aggregate and non-personal information to conduct research and to provide reports for Used Price Info business partners and customers.  

Information Sharing and Disclosure Used Price Info does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies.  
Used Price Info has no control over its advertisers' privacy policies, so please examine the privacy policy of any company advertising on the Used Price Info Web site prior to submitting any personal information. 

If you do not want your information to be used for marketing by Used Price Info and/or a third party, do not "opt in," agree to such use.  
Please note that whenever you opt in to receive future communications from a third party, your information will be subject to the third party’s privacy policy.  
If you later decide that you do not want that third party to use your information, you will need to contact the third party directly, as we have no control over how third parties use information.  
You should always review the privacy policy of any party that collects your information to determine how that entity will handle your information.  
Used Price Info will respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.  
We may transfer personal information about you if Used Price Info is acquired by or merged with another company.  
Used Price Info may display targeted advertisements based on your activity on the Used Price Info Web site, but Used Price Info does not provide your information to the advertiser in order to display the targeted ads.  

Protection of Children’s Personal Rights Used Price Info is a general audience site and does not knowingly collect any personal information from children. 

Changes to this Privacy Policy Used Price Info may occasionally update this privacy policy.  
When we do, we will also revise the "last updated" date at the top of the privacy policy.  
We encourage you to periodically review this privacy policy to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect.  
Your continued use of the service constitutes your agreement to this privacy policy and any updates.  
Please direct any questions or comments regarding our privacy policy to support@Used Price Info.com.
